Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
I love you so much.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Invites His Physcially Challenged Guests
If not because of time, I would have given you a handshake and a kiss.
I can do that by faith. Are you ready to receive it by faith?
Thank you.
I want to appreciate your coming here today.
Thank you very much for coming.
Hallelujah!
Thank you.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Invites His Physcially Challenged Guests
I am here to let you know that I want to renew my relationship and my friendship with you.
I mean, I want to improve in my relationship with you.
You are my best friends.
I want you to know that everything you have as a Christian came from God
and everything you will receive in the future will come from God.
If that is the case, giving is the beginning of blessing.
So, when I give you, I am giving to myself.
When I am giving you, don't say, "Thank you", because I am reshaping my own destiny.
It's like you are helping me.
If I am giving you and you receive it, you are the one helping me.
I don't know why you love me.
When I give you and you receive it, you are helping me.
You left your houses all the way from different states and came here.
It is more blessed to give than to receive.
Love and be loved.
Be kind and receive kindness.
Show mercy and receive mercy.
Thank you.
We are going to give each of you two bags of rice.
And we are giving each person N5,000.
The grand total is twenty million, three hundred and some thousands.
We will pay for your transport.
The 5,000 naira is your own money. Transport - we are going to pay it.
We have discussed it with the driver who brought you.
Next meeting, I will spoil you.
These are wheelchairs for you.
Thank you very much.
I want to sing for you.
Do you want to sing for me? Ok, sing for me.
T.B. Joshua, we love you forever
Amen! In the place of T.B. Joshua -
Jesus Christ, we love You forever
Clap for her!
Ok, sing.
We have a father
A very very handsome father
Oh how he loves us
We now know why we always smile
Thank you.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Invites His Physically Challenged Guests
Do you want to sing?
Prophet T.B. Joshua Invites His Physcially Challenged Guests
I want to sing.
Thank you.
Hallelujah!
After spending quality time with the physically challenged,
who have come to The SCOAN
it is time for the gifts to be distributed into their midst.
You can see the large array of wheelchairs, kindly provided by Emmanuel TV Partners worldwide
which will shortly be given out to people in dire need.
In addition to the wheelchairs, each and every physically challenged guest to The SCOAN
will be leaving with two bags of rice and the sum of 5,000 naira,
aside from their various transporation costs from their respective states and countries.
Here is the huge mountain of rice that will soon be freely given
to those present at this wonderful gathering.
Remember, God has no hands but our hands to reach out to a troubled world
with His love, compassion and generosity.
This lady painfully walks forward, assisted only by a stick despite her extreme physical disability.
She is assisted to sit in her brand-new wheelchair.
You can only imagine how much of relief this will be for her
and how much easier and less stressful her daily movement will now be,
especially since she is carrying a young baby.
Physically Challenged Guests Assisted Into Their New Wheelchairs
We should see giving as the reason for relationship
Just as receiving is the reason for a relationship as well
When we give, we receive more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting seeds that will be multiplied back to us
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
We should see giving as the reason for relationship
Those with extremely inhibiting physical challenges make their way forward
to receive their brand-new wheelchairs, courtesy of Prophet T.B. Joshua
and Emmanuel TV Partners all over the world.
Just as receiving is the reason for a relationship as well
Consider the stress and the hardship they must face on a daily basis,
just trying to move around the busy streets of Lagos or whichever state they are coming from.
These are just a few out of the thousands of physically challenged people
who have been blessed with wheelchairs, food items and cash gifts since the start of The SCOAN.
As Prophet T.B. Joshua says, "Whatever we receive from the ministry, must go back into the ministry of giving
to raise the standards of people's living, to give hope to the hopeless and help to the helpless.
When we give, we receive more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting seeds that will be multiplied back to us
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
We should see giving as the reason for relationship
Just as receiving is the reason for a relationship as well
When we give, we receive more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting seeds that will be multiplied back to us
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
Those given wheelchairs on this particular occasion wave their hands in gratitude
and appreciation to God as the charitable activities continue.
As you see the conditions of those coming forward to receive this life-changing gift,
let this be an encouragement and also a challenge to you.
There are many people with similar situations in your own community, in your own environment.
Looking the other way when you see them in trouble is equal to rejecting Christ Himself.
It is now time for the distribution of the rice and cash gifts.
The first set of people given are those who have just received their brand-new wheelchairs.
...more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting...
As Prophet T.B. Joshua says, "The value of money is not to store up properties or possessions.
The value of money is to change lives, change nations and change the world".
Many of these people came in hopeless and desperate situations.
But they are leaving with a renewed sense of hope and purpose in life,
knowing that God has not forsaken or forgotten them.
What can you do with what God has given to you to reach out to them?
One thing is clear: No one is created without a gift.
And each gift is meant to meet a need.
Find them.
...relationship
Just as receiving is the reason for a relationship as well
When we give, we receive more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting seeds that will be multiplied back to us
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
We should see giving as the reason for relationship
Just as receiving is the reason for a relationship as well
When we give, we receive more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting seeds that will be multiplied back to us
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
After receiving their gifts, the Emmanuel TV Team proceeds to assist them to leave the venue.
Every single physically challenged person who came to The SCOAN on this glorious occasion
left with a wonderful blessing and the knowledge that their physical disability
did not stop them from being a friend of God.
Their pockets were replenished, their hearts enlightened and their hopes revitalised.
As they leave with smiles and joy, radiating in their countenance,
the Emmanuel TV Team followed them carrying their two bags of rice.
Remember, as a Christian, your life is a solution to someone in trouble.
You should build your Christian life around this principle,
knowing that we serve God when we help our fellow brothers.
Our position in Christ Jesus is enhanced each time we help someone in trouble.
This is what our Lord Jesus Christ meant when He said in Matthew 25, from verse 40 to 45,
"Whatsoever you do or you fail to do to the least of my brothers, that you do unto me".
In other words, Jesus was saying here, "I have no farm where I expect you to work for me.
Or an office where I expect you to help me in checking files.
My farm and my office are your fellow brothers.
Whatever problem you help them to solve, that you do unto me".
...mutual faith, mutual love
We should see giving as the reason for relationship
Just as receiving is the reason for a relationship as well
When we give, we receive more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting seeds that will be multiplied back to us
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus...
My name is Miss Patricia Malcolm from Kwara State (Nigeria).
We are here because the man of God invited us again.
He showered us with a lot of love.
He showed us love - the love of Christ, he is expressing it to us once again.
I pray that God will continue to bless him and love him too, the way he loves us.
I am so happy today because the hospitality was so great.
We were treated well by the man of God
We have been shown love.
By giving us food and drink, we are so happy.
You can see everybody around us here; we are happy.
We are going home with two bags of rice and money in our pockets.
Thank you.
Amen. Love looks around to see those who are in need
and we thank God that you who are in need are very appreciative of the wonderful gift of God
in the life of Prophet T.B. Joshua and the Emmanuel TV Partners. God bless you.
...as the reason for relationship.
Just as receiving is the reason for a relationship as well
When we give, we receive more of whatever we give
I am Nneka Benedicta from Anambra State (Nigeria).
Pastor T.B. Joshua, we thank you. God bless him for all he has done today.
We wish him all the best with God's love and protection.
Amen. Is this your first time at this programme?
Yes.
What did you receive today?
God's love, so many things.
As you can see, we have two bags of rice and the money he gave us.
May God guide and protect him, bless him the more.
Thank you.
Just as receiving is the reason for a relationship as well
Today you are here at the meeting of the physically challenged with Prophet T.B. Joshua
and you received two bags of rice and 5,000 naira. How do you feel?
I am very happy!
I thank him very much.
May God bless him.
I pray for more blessings for him. God should bless him more.
God bless you, sir. We pray that you have a safe trip back home.
Thank you
Thank you very much. God bless you.
...more of whatever we give
When we give...
Peace be unto you!
We are thanking T.B. Joshua for the gifts and for what he has done for us.
May God bless him.
Everyone of us who are physically challenged have been blessed with a gift from him.
May God bless him more and more - a hundredfold.
Thank you.
...multiplied back to us
Every true friendship...
Hello, sir. How are you?
Fine. Thank you. God bless you.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
I pray that God will provide everything he needs.
Thank you.
...mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
Oluwole from Ekiti (Nigeria).
So you came all the way from Ekiti State to this special meeting with Prophet T.B. Joshua?
We really enjoyed the meeting with Pastor T.B. Joshua.
We are very excited about the gifts from Pastor T.B. Joshua.
What did you receive? What are you going home with?
Two bags of rice and 5,000 naira each.
Have a safe journey back home. Thank you very much for coming. Bye bye.
Please tell us your name.
I'm Pauline.
And where did you come from?
I'm coming from Abia State (Nigeria).
In fact, I can't really express myself.
I really didn't expect this. Seriously, I'm very grateful.
I pray and ask God to add more grease to his elbows.
Amen. Is this your first time?
It is my first time.
Tell us - what did you receive today?
I received a big token of 5,000 naira and two bags of rice.
And you are glad about that?
I am very glad.
Those who have been criticising the man of God,
I really don't see the reason why they should do that.
I think that the person who God has blessed, God has blessed that person
and the person who God has given a gift, He has given him that gift.
I am telling people of the world that they shouldn't criticise a man of God;
he is a very good man. God is really using him.
I am very grateful and very happy for today.
Thank you very much. And we wish you a safe journey back home
and hope to see you next time at this meeting, in Jesus' name.
Amen. Thank you.
The Physically Challenged Guests Are Assisted With Their Gifts Of Rice
We should see giving as the reason for relationship
Just as receiving is the reason for a relationship as well
When we give, we receive more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting seeds that will be multiplied back to us
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
We should see giving as the reason for relationship
Just as receiving is the reason for a relationship as well
When we give, we receive more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting...
My name is Kate Ajudua. I'm from Delta State (Nigeria).
How was the meeting for you today with Prophet T.B. Joshua?
He invited you all the way from your state to this special occasion. How do you feel?
I feel good. I want to thank the man of God.
I know that God is helping him to help those who need help.
I know that God is going to replenish his pockets.
I thank God for his life, family and ministry.
I ask God to expand his ministry and bless him the more.
Thank you.
Amen. How is this Christmas going to be different for you?
The man of God has blessed everybody and I thank God for him.
Amen. We thank God for your life. Be blessed as you go home, in Jesus' name.
Thank you very much.
Tell us your name and where you come from.
Kehinde. I come from Kehiti (Nigeria).
Are you one of those who attended the physically challenged meeting with Prophet T.B. Joshua today?
Yes. I am very happy.
Is this your first time?
No, this is not my first time. This is my second time of coming here.
Tell us - what was the gift you received today?
I received two bags of rice and 5,000 naira.
And you are happy about that?
yes,God bless T.B. Joshua.
My name is Nwafor Chukwuemeka.
We are very grateful for the man of God and his intervention.
We are very grateful.
Is this your first time?
Of course, this is my first time.
Ok, tell us - what was the gift you received today?
I received two bags of rice. You can see it here. And the sum of 5,000 naira.
People should know that the man of God is friendly to us and we are grateful for that.
Other men of God should know how to offer this kind of help.
Thank you very much. We wish you a safe journey back home.
Thank you very much.
...relationship as well
When we give, we receive more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting seeds that will be multiplied back to us
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
We should see giving as the reason for relationship
Emmanuel! You are welcome. What is your name? Where are you from?
Oladapo Coker. I'm from Lagos State (Nigeria).
And you are here today for the special meeting with Prophet T.B. Joshua.
What can you say about what took place today?
What a wonderful day. I am very happy to see today
because T.B. Joshua, the man of God, has done well for us.
More grease to his elbows.
Wonderful. Sir, what did you receive today?
I received a blessing.
What was done for me, I am very happy with it - 5,000 naira and two bags of rice.
Thank you very much.
- Safe journey back home, sir.
- Thank you.
...multiplied back to us
Hi. Tell us your name and where you are from.
My name is Chiwenda from Imo State (Nigeria).
And today you are here at the physically challenged meeting with Prophet T.B. Joshua.
What did you receive today?
I received two bags of rice and 5,000 naira.
And are you happy?
Yes, I am happy. Thank you very much.
Tell us your name and where you come from.
I am Kolawole from Osun (Nigeria).
This has been wonderful.
He has been doing it - for the past five years, I have been witnessing it.
But today's own was great!
When I saw the number of people,
I said to myself, "What people would take away today would be 1,000 naira and a bag of rice".
When the man of God said he was going to give each person 5,000, I said, "Wow! This is great!"
With this number of people, giving them 5,000 naira each and two bags of rice,
if you don't see it by yourself, you may not believe it.
But seeing is believing. I believe people are watching this at home.
They will see what is going on here.
I don't think anybody can judge anybody except on what you see.
So, we have seen a good thing today.
Thank you very much. We wish you a safe journey back home.
...mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
We should see giving as the reason for relationship
Just as receiving is the reason for a relationship as well
When we give, we receive more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting seeds that will be multiplied...
Hello, sir. Tell us your name and where you are from.
I'm from Yobe (Nigeria). Douglas Okolo.
And what are you going home with today?
I'm going home with two bags of rice and 5,000 naira. Wow!
It is what we live for.
Glory be to God. We thank God.
It is very awesome. Yes, it is awesome.
Awesome. God bless you. Safe journey home.
Thank you. The same to you. Bye bye.
My name is Chikodi.
And where do you come from?
I'm from Anambra State (Nigeria).
What did you receive today?
I received two bags of rice and 5,000 naira.
And how do you feel about that?
I am feeling fine.
Have a safe journey back to your state.
Thank you very much.
...as the reason for relationship
Chidinma from Imo State (Nigeria)
Today you have spent this wonderful occasion with us
as you were invited by the man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua to this special occasion.
Today you received 5,000 naira and two bags of rice and also a brand-new wheelchair.
How do you feel?
Very fine and good. I am so happy for that.
I am grateful to the man of God.
We thank God for the life of Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV Partners
who made this day special for you.
We pray that God Almighty who has provided all these gifts for you
will continue to supply, in Jesus name.
Amen.
Safe journey home.
Thank you very much.
My name is Busola Abidogun.
And you come from where?
Akure (Nigeria).
This is not my first time.
So you have been here before?
Yes.
In the meeting today, what did you receive?
A lot - money, rice and a wheelchair.
I really thank him. May the Lord God Almighty be with him and guide him.
People should emulate what Prophet T.B. Joshua is doing.
We wish you a safe journey back home, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Emmanuel! Indeed, God is with us.
Here we have physically challenged people.
To the glory of God, they had their meeting here with Prophet T.B. Joshua.
And they were blessed tremendously through the kind gesture of the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua,
and now they are embarking on their journey back home.
So here we have the bus that conveyed people from Ekiti State
to The SCOAN for the physically challenged meeting that just concluded some hours ago.
So right now, based on the philanthropic nature and kind gesture of the man of God,
he said we should give the money they used in transporting themselves
from their various destinations to The SCOAN.
The cost is 15,000 naira - this is it.
Now, the prophet loves you for being patient enough
to convey them from Lagos to The SCOAN.
For that reason, he said we should give you this cash gift and two bags of rice.
Now, to our coordinator.
The prophet loves you and your colleagues who are the physically challenged.
The prophet said we should give you 80,000 naira
which is the cost of your transportation from Lagos back to Ekiti State.
The cost is 80,000 naira which the prophet said we should give you.
Thank you very much. We really appreciate what Pastor T.B. Joshua did for us.
I thank him very much. May God give him long life and prosperity.
For doing this, God will bless him very well.
God will bless him so much.
We are from Ekiti State.
We really appreciate what the man of God did for us. The man is a great hero.
Thank you.
...we receive more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting seeds that will be multiplied...
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
The Physically Challenged Guests Are Transported Back To Their Various Homes With Their Gifts
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
When we give, we are planting seeds...
The physically challenged are the friends of Jesus
and also the friends of Prophet T.B. Joshua and his ministry. That is why we are here.
Austin Chima from Imo State (Nigeria).
We are happy to be here because last year, we couldn't make it.
We are here to receive what our fellow physcially disabled colleagues
have enjoyed in the past.
We were here today to receive our own and we are happy that we received our own.
We want to use this opportunity to thank our Prophet T.B. Joshua
for this kind gesture that he has done today.
Here with me is a cash gift given to the people that came from Imo State
and this is the total sum of 85,000 naira
Amputee Association Of Imo State Receive Gift Of 85,000 Naira
We give it to the leader of the group. You are welcome, sir.
Thank you for receiving it.
Thank you, sir. We are really happy. God bless you.
Thank you, Prophet T.B. Joshua! May God bless you in abundance
God bless you!
Here with me are people from other states.
And this group comes from Abia State.
By the grace of God, we are here to represent Prophet T.B. Joshua
to give this cash gift of 90,000 naira for the physcially challenged that came from Abia State.
Amputee Association Of Abia State Receive Gift Of 90,000 Naira
Blessing Agwu.
I'm one of Nigeria's goal keepers.
We came from Abia State to celebrate with Prophet T.B. Joshua
I'm one of the physically challenged.
We are very grateful that the man of God was able to do this for us.
I don't really know what to say because it is unbelievable.
I believe that God should bless him more and more, in Jesus' name.
The man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, said that we should all say,
"Thank you for receiving the gift". God bless you.
I have a word for the man of God.
I am thanking him for what he has done for us.
We are waiting for him to answer us in our world cup,
October next year in Mexico that he will sponsor us.
He has done it before; he will do it again.
How are you, sir?
Fine, sir.
Did you enjoy your coming to The SCOAN?
Yes, I enjoyed today. I thank God for Prophet T.B. Joshua.
As he has done this for us, God will bless him.
People of God, the man of God said we should pay your transportation
and that money is what we are giving to him now - 15,000 naira.
God bess you.
Also here with me, sir: The man of God said we should bless you with Christmas gift.
And this is 5,000 naira.
Thank you, sir.
And also two bags of rice.
I thank God! More promotion!
My prophet, long life and prosperity!
When we give, we are planting seeds that will be multiplied...
After bringing your group here, the man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua said
we should give to you as a driver the sum of 5,000 naira. This is for you, sir.
And two bags of rice as well.
Because we know of your effort in bringing these guys all the way to Lagos from Ebonyi.
We also have this sum for the people in the vehicle
which is transportation for them to get all the way back to Ebonyi in a safe and sound fashion.
So, this is for you - 30,000 naira.
Thank you. He has been doing it. This is not the first time I have been hearing about it.
More grease to his elbows.
I want to say thank you to the man of God who has given us this opportunity
to receive from him.
...multiplied back to us
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
Sir, you are welcome here today to The SCOAN, in Jesus' name.
We just want to appreciate you for coming here,
taking your time out to bring these people down and transporting them all the way here
to The SCOAN for the physically challenged meeting.
Because of this wonderful effort you have taken in coming and bringing people,
we have a gift here today from Prophet T.B. Joshua of 5,000 naira
as a token of thank you for just taking time to bring these people
down here today to The SCOAN.
Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV Partners have sent us to you
to present this gift of 15,000 naira for the transport of all of you here -
so your coming and going here today to the physically challenged meeting at The SCOAN
has been paid for by Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV Partners.
Two bags of rice as a token of thank you as well for coming here today
to The SCOAN and for taking an effort of bringing these people here today.
...mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
I want to thank Prophet T.B. Joshua very much.
God will bless him and his family.
I want to pray for the man of God.
May God help him, in the name of Jesus Christ.
Amen.
...mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
Thank you so much for coming.
You can see that this group of people have come and been with us
for the physically challenged meeting as they were invited by Prophet T.B. Joshua.
We want to present you here a gift of 180,000 naira
which is the transportation for everyone here in the bus.
So, driver, this is their transport money.
So you don't need to collect anything from them.
This is for you from Prophet T.B. Joshua.
We also want to give you 15,000 naira for fuel to drop them to their various destinations from there.
We also want to give you personally a gift of 5,000 naira.
We also want to present to you, the driver, two bags of rice.
...mutual love
...mutual trust
You are blessed to bless others so make sure to share what you have received today
with a cheerful heart and God will continue to supply of more.
I want to thank the man of God. More grease to his elbows.
May God guide him and his family, in Jesus' name.
...mutual love
...mutual trust, mutual faith
We have just finished the wonderful physically challenged meeting with T.B. Joshua
and our friends are about to leave on their way back to their states, on their way back home.
We just want to tell you all that the man of God has paid for your transport
and we want to give the driver right now 15,000 naira to cover your transport.
Cash Gifts, Transport Money And Rice Were Given To All The Drivers Who Transported The Physically Challenged Guests
And we know that the driver has made a lot of sacrifice to be here
and to give up his time to be with you and help you.
So we also want to give him a gift of 5,000 naira.
Cash Gifts, Transport Money And Rice Were Given To All The Drivers Who Transported The Physically Challenged Guests
We want to give the driver two bags of rice.
...love
...mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
I thank Prophet T.B. Joshua for what he has done for us.
God will continue to bless him for what he has done for us.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
...mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
The Physically Challenged Guests Are Transported Back To Their Various Homes With Their Gifts
...as the reason for relationship
Just as receiving is the reason for a relationship as well
When we give, we receive more of...
Bye bye
When we give, we receive more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting seeds that will be multiplied back to us
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
We should see giving as the reason for relationship
Just as receiving is the reason for a relationship as well
When we give, we receive more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting seeds that will be multiplied back to us
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
My name is Yemisi Salami.
I am from Akure, Women With Diabilities.
The main reason why I am here is for the man of God to help me
because walking is not easy for me.
I am a bit big; so it is not easy for me.
And today, God Almighty has met you at the point of your need.
The man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, together with the Emmanuel TV Partners from all over the world,
has provided this wheelchair for you and a cash gift of 5,000 naira
and also two bags of rice. How are you feeling now?
I am feeling very happy and very great.
I really thank the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, and the Emmanuel TV Partners.
They have been helping us.
They never leave us or make us feel that we are different.
I just want to say thank you. God bless you, continuously.
We pray that you will be in prosperous, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
You are welcome to the physically challenged meeting with T.B. Joshua
today here at The SCOAN in Lagos, Nigeria, in Jesus' name.
Tell us your name and where you are from.
My name is Abioloa Rahman.
I am from Disabled Welfare, Lagos.
Thank you very much.
Tell us the main reason why you are here at The SCOAN.
The man of God wants to bless us.
We really appreciate him.
He has been showing love and care.
We want Nigerians to emulate him.
If other people could emulate him, the way he shows love, care...
I want Nigerians to emulate the man of God.
I feel so touched that that kind of a man can be humble to assist the less privileged in society.
Wow. It is the duty of all Christians because Christians are known by their love
and the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, really knows this.
Can you please tell us about the challenges you have been facing so far.
It is not really easy - someone with a disability in Nigeria.
We are not recognised. We are neglected.
So, we are happy for someone like Prophet T.B. Joshua who can remember us.
Somebody called me that I should come.
When I came, I didn't expect to be given a wheelchair.
But I thank God. God blessed me today with the man of God.
Wow. We thank You, Jesus Christ.
It shows that Jesus Christ knows who you are,
He knows the design of your heart and He has met you today at the point of your need
through the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV Partners.
You have received today a cash gift, two bags of rice and also a wheelchair.
And how are you feeling now after receiving all these?
I feel great. I am very happy.
I pray that the good Lord will bless the church and the man of God.
Blessed be the name of the Lord; that God will bless His people and the man of God
more and more abundantly, in Jesus' name.
Amen. Thank you very much for coming.
We pray to see you again next time, in Jesus' name.
...back to us
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
We should see giving as the reason for relationship
Just as receiving is the reason for...
My name is Tunrayo Ajetunmobi.
I'm from Kwara State (Nigeria); Lagos State Disabled Association.
This is not my first time of coming here. This is my third time of coming here.
For long, I have been in need of a wheelchair
but there was nobody to help me get one.
If I walk too much, I have back pain and side pain.
So, sometimes, it would make me not to go out.
Right here at the physcially challenged meeting with T.B. Joshua,
God Almighty, Jesus Christ, has met you at the point of your need.
You have received a cash gift of 5,000 naira from the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua,
and also two bags of rice and a wheelchair as you have requested today
from the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, and the Emmanuel TV Partners from all over the world.
How are you feeling now?
I am very grateful. I thank T.B. Joshua for showing love to us.
Titilayo Mosunbola.
I am from Lagos State (Nigeria).
How did you hear about this meeting?
I've heard a lot from my friends who had been here before me
telling me the good things that the man of God has been doing for them.
He is a very friendly person with those who have been marginalised against,
like the dwarves and physically challenged persons.
So, that was why I came to this place today
with the expectation of getting a wheelchair and financial assistance.
We saw you earlier today, coming here to the physcially challenged meeting
with T.B. Joshua with your own wheelchair.
I borrowed that one; it is not my own.
It is a borrowed wheelchair.
Ok. And today God Almighty, Jesus Christ, has met you at the point of your need
through the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, together with the Emmanuel TV Partners,
to provide this wheelchair that you are sitting on right now
and also two bags of rice and a cash gift of 5,000 naira.
I am very grateful to him and I am very happy within me
and I want to use this medium to bless the man of God,
that God will bless and increase him and continue to motivate him.
More grease to his elbows.
I am also using this medium to send a message to the whole world
that people should emulate this great man of God
because he has left a legacy for us to emulate.
God will reward all the people who have been supporting.
All the workers I have seen here today have been very great. God bless you.
...love
We should see giving as the reason for relationship
Just as receiving is the reason...
Welcome to The SCOAN today. Tell us your name and where you are from.
My name is Adeyanju Dare.
I am from Lagos State (Nigeria).
You have been in the physically challenged meeting today with Prophet T.B. Joshua.
How do you feel?
I feel so great and happy. I can't express my feelings.
It is amazing. I really appreciate the man of god.
The man of God is trying and I pray for more anointing,
that God will continue to empower him and bless him more.
As he continues to bless us, so also, God will continue to bless his family.
Now tell us, what did you receive today?
Wow! I can say I received blessing, happiness and at the same time,
I received materials - what is important for me.
I really enjoyed it and I received everything - every quality thing -
two bags of rice and raw cash of 5,000 naira.
It's amazing; it's very great!
...more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting seeds that will be multiplied back to us
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
We should see giving as the reason for relationship
Just as receiving is the reason for a relationship as well
When we give, we receive more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting seeds that will be multiplied back to us
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
Hello, sir. Tell us your name and where you are from.
Adeboye Adeyanju. I am from Surelere (Nigeria).
And you were the driver of the physically challenged people you brought here today?
Yes.
Today when you came, tell us what happened.
I like what happened. Pastor Joshua is very kind.
What did you receive from Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV Partners today?
I received rice and money - 5,000 naira and two bags of rice.
And how do you feel about that?
I love this. Thank you very much.
Hello. What is your name and where are you from?
Husseni Yahyah from Katsina State (Nigeria).
You are welcome. You were here today for the physically challenged meeting with Prophet T.B. Joshua.
How did you find it?
Pastor, thank you.
I thank you. God bless you.
What did you receive today? What are you going home with?
Two bags of rice and 5,000 naira.
Thank you. God bless you.
God bless you, sir. Safe journey home.
Amen. Thank you.
Thank you. Bye bye.
Hello. Tell us your name and where are you from.
My name is Igwe Dennis.
And where are you from?
I am from Cross River State (Nigeria).
You were here today for the meeting with Prophet T.B. Joshua. How was it for you?
I loved the meeting and I believe that with Prophet T.B. Joshua,
everything is going to be okay in this coming year with us.
And what are going home with today?
Two bags of rice and such money - 5,000 naira is enough.
God bless you. We thank God for the wonderful blessing of God in your life.
- Safe journey home.
- Yes.
Hello, baba.
Yes. Thank you.
What is your name, sir? Where are you from?
Hamisu from Zamfara (Nigeria).
Thank you very much.
I pray that God will bring more in the coming year.
...relationship as well
When we give, we receive more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting seeds that will be multiplied back to us
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
So the man of God has sent us to give you your transport fare back to Asaba.
65,000 naira for everybody.
65,000 naira to give to the driver for the transport fare.
And a gift again for the driver - 5,000 naira and two bags of rice.
...mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
I want to thank the man of God, T.B. Joshua, for showing love to us.
We are richly blessed.
God will bless him and keep his ministry going on stronger and stronger, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
God should bless him for blessing us, caring for us
and taking care of people with disabilities.
God will bless him more and put money where he took this one from
to provide for us, in Jesus' name. Amen.
Bye!
...mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
Sir, bless tell us your name and where you are from.
Mutairu
And you are the driver of this bus?
Yes.
The man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, is giving you 5,000 naira.
This is a personal gift for you as the driver.
And he is also giving you this cash gift of 15,000 naira
which is the money for the vehicle to transport you both from and to your state.
That is for you.
Long life, T.B. Joshua. God bless him.
Bye bye.
...mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
By the grace of God, the man of God has provided your transport fare from Lagos to Kware State.
17,000 naira
Moreover, the man of God has given the driver 5,000 naira as a gift and two bags of rice.
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual love...
Kamorudeen Balogun from Kware State (Nigeria).
We really appreciate what the man of God did for us.
He really shows a lot of love, just as Jesus said it should be shown.
May he be blessed. May he grow from strength to strength.
May this church never perish.
May the people who come here always receive their miracle
because we have all been made happy. As we are happy,
may the blessing of the Lord descend on the man of God and his workers.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
My name is Adam Mohammed.
I was born in Kano State but I am living in Kware State (Nigeria).
We are members of the Para Sport Team in Kwara State.
This is the first time we came to play a friendly match against Lagos State
and we heard the information that T.B. Joshua was helping the disabled.
We give thanks for everything. That was why we came.
We have seen appreciate everything. We thank you very much.
God bless him and bless us.
What gift did you receive today?
My colleagues and I received two bags of rice and 5,000 naira each.
I really appreciate everything.
I would like to say thank you to everybody.
This is something that we have witnessed with our own eyes.
It is not what people have been saying. It is not fake; it is a reality
and we saw it with our own eyes.
Each person recieved their own gift. I thank God for everything.
We really appreciate.
The anointed man of God is also giving every member of this team the total sum of 70,000 naira -
from the anointed man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV Partners.
This is just for your transport back to where you have come from.
Thank you very much. We wish you a safe journey back, in Jesus' name.
Amen. Thank you very much.
My name is Haruna Mohammed. I come from Sokoto (Nigeria).
I am the driver of these - my brothers.
They asked me to drive them to this place; so, that's why I brought them here.
And what did you witness today?
I saw that they gave everybody 5,000 naira and two bags of rice each.
So, I am really happy about that.
The anointed man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, and Emmanuel TV Partners
are also giving you as their driver the gift of 5,000 naira.
This is 5,000 naira.
And also the sum of 15,000 naira for their transportation.
The man of God also said that we should give you two bags of rice as well.
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual love...
Thank you very much.
...for a relationship as well
When we give, we receive more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting seeds that will be multiplied back to us
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
We should see giving...
Praise the Lord!
So, today we had a wonderful meeting here.
This is the vehicle that came from Yobe (Nigeria).
The man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, The SCOAN and Emmanuel TV Partners
are giving you this wonderful gift of your transportation from Lagos State to Yobe State.
This is 112,000 naira.
Cash Gifts, Transport Money And Rice Were Given To All The Drivers Who Transported The Physically Challenged Guests
You hold it. It is for your transportation from Lagos State to Yobe State.
Now, here we have more.
15,000 - this is for your transportation within Lagos State.
And here we have 5,000 naira which is for our driver here
who has brought you here and is taking you back.
For the driver.
Praise the Lord!
Hallelujah!
We also have two bags of rice for our driver.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Carry your rice.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
On behalf of my people from Yobe State, I am very delighted
with what Prophet T.B. Joshua has done for us.
I pray that God will continue to enrich his purse.
Amen!
The SCOAN shall continue to grow in leaps and bounds.
Thank you very much. Praise the Lord!
Hallelujah!
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
On behalf of our father in the Lord, Prophet T.B. Joshua,
we believe you have enjoyed yourselves
and you have received a lot of things to give thanks to Jesus.
So for this reason, the man of God has decided to bless you
since you have decided to honour his invitation.
So right here with me, I have an envelope.
This one contains transportation for everyone inside the vehicle - 15,000 naira.
And here with me, sir, this is a gift from our father in the Lord, T.B. Joshua - 5,000 naira.
And here with me are also two bags of rice.
God bless you!
We thank our pastor, Pastor Temitope Joshua - a man of the people.
...love
We should see giving as the reason for relationship
Praise the Lord!
Hallelujah!
You know that Jesus loves you.
Thank you for coming here and thank you for accepting the gift.
Hallelujah!
The man of God has said you are blessed.
And all your transport from here to your home, the man of God has paid everything.
You don't need to pay anything. Everything is provided for.
So, driver, this is a blessing for you.
This is for you personally. 5,000 for you.
And the man of God gives you two bags of rice.
The Prophet has provided 15,000 to pay for your transport back home.
Just as receiving is the reason for a relationship as well
When we give...
My name is Oluwaseyi Ojerinde.
I want to thank the man of God. He always cares for us.
God will bless him more and more. Thank you.
Thank you. God bless you.
My name is Omobolanle Adams.
I thank our father for remembering us again.
We give glory to the Lord for all that he has done for us.
May the Lord continue to bless him and all the members, in Jesus' name.
God bless you. Thank you.
When we give, we receive more of whatever...
We have here 5,000 naira for the driver of the bus. That is for you, sir.
And two bags of rice.
That is not all. We also have 15,000 naira here for all your transportation back home again.
T.B. Joshua, I thank you very much. God bless you.
...we are planting seeds that will be multiplied back to us
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
Thank you, Man of God!
Bye.
...back to us
Every true friendship in Christ...
My name is Oluwaseyi David. We came from Rivers State (Nigeria).
Which group is this?
This is Disabled Welfare Sports.
This is our first time.
We each received 5,000 naira gifts and two bags of rice.
We are very happy.
The anointed man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, as he has promised,
he is paying for your transport fare back to your state - Rivers State.
That is the sum of 40,000 naira for the eight of you. This is the money.
We thank the man of God. God will continue to bless him, in Jesus' name.
Anything he lays his hands upon shall prosper, in Jesus' name.
Amen. Thank you very much. We wish you a safe journey back.
My name is Wasiu Yusuf.
From Osun State (Nigeria). Physically challenged.
This is the transport money that is for you and all the people that came with you
from the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
I want to thank T.B. Joshua. I am very happy about the gifts he gave us,
including the money for transport.
God will bless T.B. Joshua. Amen.
Thank you very much. Let us also hear from the driver who is going to take this group back to their state.
I am Wasiu Dada; a driver from Osun State (Nigeria).
I transported them here.
Driver, what we have here is the transport fee
for the group of people that came all the way from Osun State so they don't owe you anything.
The man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua is the one paying for their transport back to their state.
Sir, this is an amount of 15,000 naira.
I really thank T.B. Joshua and the entire members of the church.
We also have another special gift for you from the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua,
for your effort to bring this group to The SCOAN.
In addition to that, Prophet T.B. Joshua is also blessing you with these two bags of rice.
So, you have in total received 5,000 naira from the man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua and two bags of rice
to bless you for bringing our friends to The SCOAN.
I don't know what to say. I am thanking the members of the church,
the whole crew and T.B. Joshua - more grease to his elbows and long life.
...must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
And right now we are with the people who have been blessed by the man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Right now we are with the driver with the gift that the man of God has given the driver
which is 5,000 naira and two bags of rice for the driver himself.
I say thank you. I am so grateful for what the man of God is doing in my life.
I am so grateful. Thank you.
I am very grateful to Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Thank you for what you have been doing for us. We are very grateful.
I am happy.
Just as receiving is the reason for a relationship as well
When we give, we receive more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting seeds that will be multiplied back to us
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
Bye bye.
When we give, we receive more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting seeds that will be multiplied back to us
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
We should see giving as the reason for relationship
Just as receiving is the reason for a relationship as well
When we give, we receive more of whatever we give
When we give, we are planting seeds that will be multiplied back to us
Every true friendship in Christ Jesus must be mutual trust, mutual faith, mutual love
Man of God, thank you for today!
The Physically Challenged Guests of Prophet T.B. Joshua With Their Gifts Bound For Home
TO GOD BE THE GLORY!